Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real?
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times!
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
That we're looking for?
There's always room for you!
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise!
We are
Ah! Ah!
Ahhhh!
Huh?
Ah!
Ahhhhh!
Aaaaah!
Is his arm okay?
If he took a single step back, his
arm would have been ripped off.
Yeah, but he wasn't thinking
about how animal fangs work;
that'd require a tiny bit of brain power.
Is he okay?
You think Big Bro
Luffy's arm will make it?
Hey, where'd he go?
Luffy, the sea!
Hey, look, a shark!
No, that's Arlong!
So wait, you an under?
Oh, crap.
This isn't good.
His abilities double in
strength when he's underwater.
Once my momentum in the water builds
up, it's impossible to stop me.
This is precisely the kind of ability that
makes us fishmen all the more superior.
Did he run away?
Ah, it's time.
Soap!
Oh no!
A torpedo?
Something just flew out of the sea!
Wow!
Wow.
I'm impressed you could
dodge that. Good job.
But the longer you evade your
death, the more painful it will be.
Shark... DOGE!
Whoa.
Just what kind of bones
does that crazy shark have?
His nose crushed the ground.
Charge!
Hey, Luffy, hide!
Marlon went into the sea again!
Hurry up, Big Bro, you
gotta hide from him.
He's setting his sights on you right now.
Get out of there!
I won't hide.
Stop being so stupid.
Go run for cover before you
become a target. No way!
I'm not running anywhere.
I'm gonna catch him and break his nose.
Ya shark!
You got some nerve.
Or you realize that it's
pointless to try and hide from me.
Did you hear us telling you that
you should go somewhere and hide?
You barely escaped his last attacks!
If he lands just one
direct hit, it'll kill you!
Luffy, listen to us!
Go and hide!
Now Gum-Gum!
SHIELD!
Hey wait, what's that position?
I don't think that'll stop the attack.
I'll get double the
speed from this distance.
This time I'll pierce
your heart, Weber Man.
Now, take this!
SHOTTERS!
He's here!
Oh no!
Did he get hit? He's fine.
He somehow managed to avoid it.
It's over!
That attack won't work now!
Sure, die!
You bastard!
I was just pure luck!
That's it!
Gum-Gum!
Paper nine!
Is he dead?
Do you see the intensity in his eyes?
Oh no, it's the same expression that
sea kings make before they snap!
He must have snapped
with Luffy's last attack?
His eyes!
I've never seen them like that.
You wretched human!
What have you done to me?
A mighty fish man!
Whoa, that was crazy.
It didn't actually hurt, but I can
tell he's really, like, madder.
Oh man, what was that?
The saw blade!
That thing is gigantic!
Aaaaaah!
Aaaaaah! Aaaaaah!
Micro Luffy! Micro Luffy!
He won't stop!
Luffy will get cornered!
Aaaaaah! Aaaaaah! Aaaaaah! Aaaaaah!
He jumped in the building!
the left window on the top floor.
that's the room that.
there's nowhere else to run.
you and me here in the highest
level of our long park.
what is this room?
a lot of paper.
this isn't just any room.
This is the room where I make Nami
draw all of her C-charts for me.
The nap room!
This is Nami's room?
These C-charts are what she's
worked on all these years.
There is no one else on
the face of the planet that
can draw C-charts with such
accuracy and efficiency.
That young lady has a gift.
And there really isn't anything as ultimately
regrettable as wasting natural talent.
Staying here and drawing
up C-Charts for me is
her only chance at living
up to her full potential.
This pen is stained with blood.
In order for me to attain world supremacy,
her C-Charts are absolutely vital.
She will continue drawing her
C-Charts for my own ambitions.
And once her charts give me full
knowledge of all the world's oceans.
We fishmen will be totally invincible!
And the world shall kneel before us.
The first step is this island.
Then we'll move on to the whole East Blue.
You could never use her like me?
She would be wasted on you.
What the?
The shark cell.
It won't budge.
Now!
Use her!
What's happening?
Are they still fighting?
What's going on up there?
Damn it, big bro Luffy, are you okay?
I wish we knew what was going on up there.
Luffy, you bastard.
What do you take her for?
She's an inferior creature, but
she has risen far above her peers.
If all other humans are sewer rats,
then she's a feisty little kitten.
After all, she is adorable.
She has her place, and
it's here beside me.
Can't you understand that?
I can give her everything she needs.
And the only thing she has to do is continue
drawing those marvelous charts for me.
So Nami will forever be my tool or no?
She'll be my friend.
What is that?
A desk.
It's a desk.
It's okay.
It was just a desk. Man. I was scared.
I thought that was big.
Bro.
Luffy.
For sure.
Hold on.
I don't want to hear that
kind of talk from you.
Have you lost your faith? What?
No.
You were scared too. Johnny.
Don't be stupid.
I just uh well you know.
I thought it was Arlong.
Flying through the air.
What a load of crap.
You were scared. Admit. Admit.
What you jerk. Admit that.
I know Arlong's going down.
There's no way that big bro Luffy
is going to lose this fight.
Whoa.
What's going on?
Why is all that stuff
being thrown out of there?
Alright, as of today,
this will be your room,
your desk, your pens, everything
you'll need is in here.
Stop it now!
The charts!
My charts!
Dumb rat, you can't trick me that easily.
Trying to draw up fake charts.
I can't believe you waste your time!
Drawing crap like this in secret.
If you ever try to pull
a stunt like this again?
I'll drag all those villagers in here!
And make you watch as I
crush every single one!
Just like with her.
Damn you!
That's eight years worth of work,
eight years of planning and ambition!
Fell in here, don't you know?
Wow, this fight is so freaking intense.
Yeah, a fight to the death, definitely.
Thank you.
Now you've got too far!
You keep jabbering on about
how much better fish men are,
and how much you need those sea charts.
I don't understand
anything about that stuff.
I've finally figured out how to save her!
This room isn't anything
but our jail cell.
There's only one way for Nami to escape.
I've got to tear this place apart.
Conker!
You fool.
Arlong Park cannot be brought
down by some inferior human,
especially not by some
rubbery freak like you!
Start to drown!
Oh, shit!
Oh no!
It looks like Arlong Park is coming down!
It's gonna collapse!
Everybody run for cover!
Make sense! We gotta go!
Luffy's still inside!
Make sense! We can't!
Luffy!
Luffy...
It's... Luffy.
What the hell?
What's that noise?
Roofing.
Warlong Park has fallen.
Big bro.
I just wonder what went on in there.
We gotta know who won?
With all that debris!
Looks like?
Luffy?
It's Luffy!
Big bro? No!
He's just standing there. What's wrong?
NAMI!
YOU 'LL ALWAYS BE MY
Fire
Yeah.
Now I'm done, I'll keep you near.
As I drift away, I pray you'll
watch me as I disappear!
As I watch the sunrise, I begin to wonder?
What could be the reason
it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you!
Show me how to catch those feelings.
Get them to come back to me!
I'll do what I must be.
Cause they're everything I want to be!
Wrap these arms around my dreams.
And pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands for you,
I'm sure that we can make a way?